<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>news on CAPE|全球青年实践网络</title>
    <link>http://www.hicape.com/tags/news/</link>
    <description>Recent content in news on CAPE|全球青年实践网络</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2013 10:33:58 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://www.hicape.com/tags/news/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Vizio Thin &amp; Light: Something New and Edgy</title>
      <link>http://www.hicape.com/2013/03/vizio-thin-light-something-new-and-edgy/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2013 10:33:58 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.hicape.com/2013/03/vizio-thin-light-something-new-and-edgy/</guid>
      <description>Last year was very eventful in the notebook world. Beyond the UX upheaval brought on by Windows 8 and the blurring of the line between notebooks and tablets, we’ve seen two high-profile entrants to the realm of notebook PC hardware, Razer and Vizio. Both are well established tech companies that have experience shipping high-quality products in their respective gaming and HDTV market areas. This type of thing doesn’t happen very often, and while it’s not on the level of Microsoft jumping into the PC hardware ring, it’s an interesting trend to note. Contrary to Razer’s focused, single-device launch targeting the gaming market, Vizio jumped into the mainstream PC game head first, debuting three different products—an Ultrabook, a notebook, and an all-in-one. Given Vizio’s history of delivering solid, high-resolution LCD HDTVs on a budget, these systems were pretty highly anticipated, with cutting edge industrial design and high-grade style on a relative budget, but definitely had some usability issues at launch. After the Windows 8 update though, it seemed like some of those issues would be fixed and the post-holiday sales have made them very tempting options in the ultraportable space. Today we’ll be looking at their Thin+Light Ultrabook, which</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>